A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
- Publications, 1907-1965, 1990, 4.475 cubic feet (Box 30, 41-52)
  - VEPCO Publications, 1925-1959, 1990, 2.675 cubic feet (Box 30, 41-48 and oversize map drawer)
    - Accomplishments in Rural Electrification in Virginia by VEPCO, submitted in competition for the Thomas W. Martin Award (4 of 4), 1955 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Accomplishments in the Promotion of Electric Water Systems by VEPCO, submitted in competition for the Frank Watts Award (1 of 2), 1955 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Accomplishments in the Promotion of Electric Water Systems by VEPCO, submitted in competition for the Frank Watts Award (2 of 2), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Accomplishments in the Promotion of Electric Water Systems by VEPCO, submitted in competition for the Frank Watts Award (1 of 2, copy 2), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Accomplishments in the Promotion of Electric Water Systems by VEPCO, submitted in competition for the Frank Watts Award (2 of 2, copy 2), 1955 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Charters, Franchises, Etc. of the Various Companies Comprising the Norfolk Railway and Light Company, n. d. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Chronological corporate chart, 1937 (Map-case G-14, Drawer 20, Folder 10)
    - General Instructions Covering Erection of Leffel Vertical Turbines, n. d. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - John E. Harvell, biographical sketch and honorary tribute, n. d. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Virginia Railway and Power Company publications, 1917-1990 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company: Waterpower Equipment, n. d. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - North Anna Nuclear Power Plant pamphlets and promotional material, n. d. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - North Anna Power Station emergency planning and information calendar, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Report No. 2326 on Virginia Western Power Company and the Charlottesville and Albemarle Railway Company, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Statement of the Virginia Railway and Power Company in the Matter of the Pending Applications of the Richmond and Henrico Railway Company for Competitive Franchises, n. d. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Summary of Accomplishments, Electric Light and Power, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Summary of Accomplishments, Electric System, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Summary of Accomplishments, Electric System, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Summary of Accomplishments, Electric System, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Summary of Accomplishments, Electric System, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award (copy 2), 1929 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Summary of Accomplishments, Sales Department, 1 July 1929-30 June 1930, submitted in competition for the Stone and Webster Sales Contest, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Summary of Accomplishments, Sales Department, 1 July 1929-30 June 1930, submitted in competition for the Stone and Webster Sales Contest (copy 2), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - 12th Street Station modernization report, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Vepcovian, Volume 1, 1927 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Vepcovian, Volumes 21-22, 1947-1948 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Vepcovian, Volume 33, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Public Service Company: Summary of Accomplishments, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award, 1928 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Public Service Company: Summary of Accomplishments, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award (copy 2), 1928 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Public Service Company: Summary of Accomplishments, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award, 1929 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Public Service Company: Summary of Accomplishments, submitted in competition for the Charles A. Coffin Award, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Public Service Company: Summary of Accomplishments, submitted in competition for the L. E. Myers Award, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company: Man to Man Talks, August-September 1919 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company: Public Service Chat (Norfolk newsletter), 1916-1918 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company: Public Service News (Richmond newsletter), 1918-1919 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company: Public Service News (Richmond newsletter), 1916-1917 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company: skip stop trolley line reference cards, n. d. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - American Electrical Railway Association Publications, 1914-1923, .45 cubic feet (Box 48-49)
    Comprises publications of the American Electrical Railway Association.
    - Anti-Jitney Legislation, a summary of measures taken by public authorities to regulate and restrict the use of motor vehicles in competition with street cars, 1921 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Anti-Jitney Legislation, a summary of measures taken by public authorities to regulate and restrict the use of motor vehicles in competition with street cars (copy 2), 1921 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Information regarding jitneys (chart), 1920 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Jitney Regulation: a Compilation of Statements in Technical Press Publications from January 1918 to Date, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Jurisdiction of Public Utility Commissions over Jitneys, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Public Utility Laws, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (1 of 2), 1922 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Public Utility Laws, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (2 of 2), 1922 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part II, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (1 of 2), 1922 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part II, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (2 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part III, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (1 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part III, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (2 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part IV, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (1 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part IV, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (2 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part V, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (1 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part V, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (2 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part VI, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (1 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part VI, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (2 of 2), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part VII, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part VIII, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (1 of 2), 1923 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Public Utility Laws, Part VIII, a summary of the laws creating the state public utility commissions (2 of 2), 1923 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - State vs. Local Regulation of Public Utilities, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Summary of Decisions of Public Service Commissions of Various States re: Jitney Regulations, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Other Publications, 1907-1965, 1.35 cubic feet (Box 49-52)
    Contains publications not published by VEPCO, their subsidiaries or the American Electrical Railway Association.
    - Analysis of the Electric Railway Problem, by Delos F. Wilcox, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Annual report of the auditor of the City of Richmond, 31 January 1914 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Application of the Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia for Revision of Rates, State Corporate Commission opinion and order, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Arkansas General Assembly Act No. 571: an act to create the Arkansas Corporation Commission, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - American Committee for Armenian and Syrian Relief news bulletin, February 1919 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Baltimore Gas and Electric News, March 1915 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Bridgewater Milling Corporation of Fredericksburg vs. Fredericksburg Power Company, Inc., Circuit Court case, Spotsylvania County, Volume 1, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - California Public Utilities Act, 1919 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Case and Comment, November 1913 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Corporations and Municipalities and Their Reciprocal Relations, speech by undetermined, n. d. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Edison Monthly, March 1915 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Electric railway mail case before the Interstate Commerce Commission, n. d. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - The Electric Building (VEPCO building in Richmond), n. d. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Electrical Review, 9 January 1915 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Electrical World, 10 October 1914 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Electrical World, 26 December 1914 and 2 January 1915 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Facts on Municipal Ownership in 268 Towns and Cities, by Glenn Marston, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Federal Electric Railways Report to the President, August 1920 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Isolated Plant, January 1915 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - The Jitney Bus in San Diego: a Review of Its Cause and Its Effect, and the Necessity for Its Regulation, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - The Jitney Busses, the Richmond Public and the Virginia Railway and Power Company, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - The Jitney from the Community Standpoint, the report to the transportation committee of the Oakland, California, Chamber of Commerce, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Jitneys and the Public Interest, a speech by Edmund Wakelee, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Maine Public Utilities Commission: rules and regulations governing jitneys, 10 October 1921 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Maryland General Assembly: Public Service Commission Law amendments, 1910 and 1920 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts Legislature: General and Special Acts and Resolves, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, undetermined dates (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous organizational histories, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous publications, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - MIscellaneous printed sketches, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous speeches, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Monthly Rate Letter, (Norton, Bird and Whitman newsletter), October 1916 and January 1917 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - National Electric Light Association Bulletin, September and November-December 1914 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - New Hampshire: Laws Relating to the Duties of the Public Service Commission, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - New Hampshire Public Service Commission: Rules and Regulations Governing the Operation of Jitneys, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - The Past - Interesting, The Present - Intriguing, The Future - Bright: A Story of VEPCO, by Erwin H. Will 1965 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Proceedings of the American Institute of Electrical Engineers, January 1915 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Public Service Magazine, November 1913 and August 1914 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Railway Freight Rates: The Legal, Economic, and Accounting Principles Involved in Their Judicial Determination, by Maurice H. Robinson, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Relation of Highways and Motor Transport to Other Transportation Agencies, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Report of the Executive Council of the American Federation of Labor to the 34th Annual Convention, 1914 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Richmond ordinance to regulate the use of streets for jitney operation, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Southern News Bulletin, August-September 1915 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Stone and Webster Journal, January 1921 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Stone and Webster, 1889-1989: A Century of Integrity and Service, by David Neal Keller. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Surry Nuclear Plant pamphlets, n. d. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Syracuse Lighting Commission: Report to the Mayor and Common Council, 1907 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Tennesse Jitney Law: Opinion of the United States District Court Sustaining the Constitutionality of the Law, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Three-Cent Light in Cleveland, by H. W. Wilson, n. d. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Traffic World, 17 April 1915 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - The Trend of Regulation: Some Decisions and Opinions of Courts and Commissions Which Are of Importance to Electric Railways, February 1920 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Motor Vehicle Title Law, n. d. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - West Virginia Public Service Commission report, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Wiconsin law relating to the operation of motor vehicles for the carriage of passengers for hire upon streets and highways, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Right-Of-Way Plats, 1905, 1909, 1928, .675 (Box 30, 52-53)
  These are blueprints for plats of right-of-way property belonging to the Richmond and Chesapeake Railway, a VEPCO subsidiary. Arranged by adjacent property holder's surname. There is also a bound volume of court documents, 1928, pertaining to VEPCO right-of-ways.
  - Right-of-way plats - A, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Right-of-way plats - B, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Right-of-way plats - C, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Right-of-way plats - D, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Right-of-way plats - F, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Right-of-way plats - G, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Right-of-way plats - H, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Right-of-way plats - J, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Right-of-way plats - L, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Right-of-way plats - M, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Right-of-way plats - N, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Right-of-way plats - P, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Right-of-way plats - R, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Right-of-way plats - S, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Right-of-way plats - T, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Right-of-way plats - U, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Right-of-way plats - W, 1905 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Right-of-way plats - Y, 1905 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Right-of-way plats - miscellaneous, 1905 (Box-folder 30:15 and 53:2)
  - Right-of-way plats - court documents in reference to, compiled 1 October 1928 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Right-of-way plats - map showing tracks of Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1909 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Photographs, ca. 1905-ca. 1995 (Box 54-61)
  Principally contains photographs of executives in the late 1980's and 1990's, the Twelfth Street Power Station in Richmond and other electric plants and substations, power lines and other electrical structures. There are also photographs of VEPCO staff functions from the 1920's-1950's and Richmond street photographs showing electrical and trolley lines.
  - Annual report photographs, 1950's-1960's (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Branch and company headquarters buildings, 1920's-1960's (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Chemical lab, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Electric substations - A ca. 1930's-ca. 1960's (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Electric substations - B, ca. 1930's-ca. 1960's (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Electric substations - Ballentine (Norfolk), ca. 1950's-ca. 1960's (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Electric substations - Buggs Island (Roanoke), 1950's-1960's (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Electric substations - Chesterfield-Lakeside-Possum Point, construction, 1956-1957 (Box 54, Folder 8-14)
  - Electric substations - Chesterfield transmission, ca. 1940's-ca. 1950's (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Electric substations - Customer's (Norfolk), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Electric substations - Customer's (Peninsula), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Electric substations - Customer's (Petersburg), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Electric substations - Customer's (Richmond), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Electric substations - Customer's (Southside), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Electric substations - Customer's (Suffolk), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Electric substations - D and E, ca. 1920's-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Electric substations - Dooms (Blue Ridge), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Electric substations - East Highland Park (Richmond), ca. 1940 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Electric substations - Embrey Power Station (Fredericksburg), 1930's-1940's (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Electric substations - F, 1930's-1940's (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Electric substation - Fredericksburg, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Electric substations - G, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Electric substations - H, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Electric substations - I, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Electric substations - Indoor (Richmond), 1928-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 14-16)
  - Electric substations - J, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Electric substations - K, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Electric substations - L, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Electric substations - M, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Electric substations - McGlaughlin Substation (Norfolk), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Electric substations - Manchester Power Station (Richmond), ca. 1930-ca. 1950, Also see 12th Street Substation (Richmond) (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Electric substations - N, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Electric substations - O, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
  - Electric substations - Old Roanoke Rapids Hydroelectric Power Station (North Carolina), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Electric substations - P, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Electric substations - Peninsula, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Electric substations - portable (Richmond), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Electric substations - Portsmouth, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Electric substations - Possum Point, heavy fuel oil construction, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Electric substations - Quantico outdoor, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Electric substations - R, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Electric substations - Reeves Avenue (Norfolk), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 56, Folder 17-18)
  - Electric substations - Reeves Avenue (Norfolk), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
  - Electric substations - Richmond, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Electric substations - Rich Square (North Carolina), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Electric substations - Ronceverte Steam Plant, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Electric substations - S, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Electric substations - Seventh Street (Richmond), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Electric substations - Stafford Outdoor, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Electric substations - Staunton, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Electric substations - Suffolk, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Electric substations - Tinsberry, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Electric substations - Twelfth Street (Richmond), ca. 1930-ca. 1950, Also see Manchester substation (Box 57, Folder 13-15)
  - Electric substations - Twelfth Street (Richmond) boilers, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Electric substations - Twelfth Street (Richmond) turbines, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
  - Electric substations - W, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 58, Folder 3-5)
  - Electric substations - West (Richmond), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Electrical equipment - gas turbines, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Electrical equipment - poles (erecting of), ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Electrical equipment - transformers, ca. 1930-ca. 1950 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Employees, [_] Ahladas, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Employees - William W. Berry (chairman of the board), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Employees - William H. Blackwell Jr. (vice president of East District), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Employees - Paul J. Bonavia (vice president of regulation), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Employees - Sam Brown, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Employees - Thomas N. Chewning (vice president, treasurer and corporate secretary), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Employees - William W. Clayton (vice president of Central Division), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Employees - Bill Davis (Virginia Public Service Company), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Employees - Paul G. Edwards (vice president of public affairs), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Employees - [_] Ellis, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Employees - Jack H. Ferguson (president and ceo), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Employees - George Gibson, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Employees - Dutch Hermann, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Employees - Donald T. Herrick Jr. (vice president of information systems), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Employees - [_] Hill, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Employees - Charles M. Jarvis (vice president of regulation), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Employees - [_] Johnson, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Employees - H. L. Leidheiser, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Employees - Randolph DeWitt McIver (vice president of central division), 1993 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Employees - miscellaneous and unidentified, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 3-5)
  - Employees - John I. Oatts (executive vice president), 1993 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Employees - Payroll Department (Richmond), ca. 1940's (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Employees - Social functions (Belle Isle Safety Picnic), 1931 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Employees - Social functions (Christmas Party at William Byrd Hotel), ca. 1930's (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Employees - Social functions (miscellaneous and unidentified), 1930's (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Employees - Arthur Stevens, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Employees - [_] Stewart, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Employees - C. K. Tribble, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Employees - Jack L. Wilson (assistant vice president of nuclear operations), 1993 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Flood (Richmond), August 1969 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Flood (Hurricane Agnes - Richmond and Petersburg), July 1972 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Historic Norfolk, n. d. (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Historic Richmond, n. d. (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Lake Jackson Dam (Prince William County), n. d. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous and unidentified, n. d. (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous and unidentified, n. d. (Box 60, Folder 1-10)
  - Norfolk gas plant, construction of gas holder, 1928 (Box 60, Folder 11-12)
  - Norfolk headquarters building construction, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear power plants, n. d. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Orange (Va.) ice plant, ca. 1930's (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Promotional demonstrations and classes, 1930's-1960's (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
  - Rappahannock and Rapidan Rivers, 1923-1943 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Richmond new office building construction, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 4-5)
  - Service trucks and streetcars, n. d. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Store-front VEPCO signs, n. d. (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Advertisements, 1955-1970, Approx. .65 cubic feet. (Map-case G-14, Drawer 19-20)